thiinkle.com 2013-12-07

# Save Hi | Privacy Policy

SaveHi.com (Christopher Wilson) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This policy covers how SaveHi.com treats personal information that SaveHi.com collects and receives through this web site. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SaveHi.com does not own or control, or to people that SaveHi.com does not employ or manage, or to information collected other than by means of this web site.

Information Collection and Use

General

  * SaveHi.com collects personal information when you register with SaveHi.com, when you use SaveHi.com products or services, when you visit SaveHi.com pages or the pages of certain SaveHi.com partners. SaveHi.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
  * When you register, we ask for information such as your name, email address, company name and address. Once you register with SaveHi.com and sign in to our services, or provide your information so that we can provide services to you, you are not anonymous to us.
  * SaveHi.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of products and services that we offer.
  * SaveHi.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, SaveHi.com cookie information, and the page you request.
  * SaveHi.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * SaveHi.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with SaveHi.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help SaveHi.com communicate with you about offers from SaveHi.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of SaveHi.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
    * We transfer information about you if SaveHi.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, SaveHi.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
    * We share your information (whether in return for compensation or otherwise) with various vendors, suppliers, and advertisers who wish to do business, or attempt to do business, with you. While we use good faith efforts to verify that such vendors, suppliers, and advertisers promote products and services of interest to site users, we cannot, and do not, endorse such vendors, suppliers, advertisers, products or services unless we expressly state otherwise. 
    * If you wish us to refrain from providing your personally identifiable information in this manner, please see the opt-out information and contact information provided below. Please note that we will continue to keep your information to the extent that it is necessary to maintain our repationship with you and that an opt-out sent to us after we have passed on your information to a third party will not affect use by that third party of your information.
    * Without limiting any other right that we reserve in our terms of use or this privacy policy, you give to us and to those to whom we provide your information the right to contact you and to attempt to sell to you one or more motor vehicles. This includes, without limitation, packaging your information and providing it, for consideration or otherwise, to persons who purchase and/or repurchase your packaged information as a sales lead. You grant your permission for us to do this (and to do all other things reasonably necessary to accomplish this putrpose) and for one or more recipients of the information to try to sell you a motor vehicle. The uses of your information are not limited to sales of motor vehicles. Please see our privacy policy for more details..

CAN-SPAM, Telephone Consumer Protection Act and Similar Law.

Your use of a this web site establishes a business or other applicable relationship with us for purposes of CAN-SPAM, the Telephone Consumer Protection Act, and all other applicable law that addresses unsolicited commercial communications. By accessing, or continuing to access, this Web Site, you agree that we or our agents or persons to whom we provide your information may call, e-mail, or otherwise communicate with you regarding promotion of the sale, lease, or exchange of goods, services, real property, or any other thing of value.

Cookies

  * SaveHi.com may set and access SaveHi.com cookies on your computer.

A few important things you should know about cookies are that:

  * We offer certain features that are only available through the use of cookies.
  * We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status.
  * Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session.
  * You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the Site.

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

  * You can edit your SaveHi.com Account Information at any time.
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the SaveHi.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the SaveHi.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your SaveHi.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
  * You can delete your SaveHi.com account by contacting us. Certain information might remain in our archived records even after your account has been deleted.

Account Password

The following information pertains to your password if one is issued. Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters, and special characters and do not disclose your SaveHi.com password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify SaveHi.com and change your password. 

Confidentiality and Security

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.
  * Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

Choice/Opt-out

Users who no longer wish to receive newsletters or promotional materials or have their information provided to third parties may opt to not receive such communications or have information shared by contacting us using the information below. We will comply with such requests as soon as is commercially practicable. Such compliance may involve batch processing and other processes that take 30 days or longer. If you opt not to receive such communications or allow us to share your information and then give your personal information to us again using a site or under other circumstances that permit us to use your information, we will regard your opt-out as rescinded. 

In most cases, it is impractical for use to stop any other party to whom we have supplied your information from continuing to use the information and opting out will usually not stop others to whom we have provided your information from continuing to use it.

To change your preference with regard to the way your information is treated:

customerservice@carclearancedeals.com  

Changes to this Privacy Policy

SaveHi.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your SaveHi.com account or by placing a notice on our site 

Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, please contact us at:   
SaveHi.com   
Privacy Policy Requests   
135 N Center St. #572   
Mesa, AZ 85211-0572 

support@savehi.com  
480-331-1259 

NOTICE: 

[Click here ](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/consumer.shtm)for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.
